Mohamed Ait Dahane

Full Stack Engineer

(a) +33 625 91 48 83

aitdahane.github.io

Profile

With more than 3 years of work experience as a full stack developer and with a software engineering grade, I have acquired strong skills in designing and building web applications.

Otherwise, I am very passionate about new technologies and I have the ambition to contribute in this field. Currently, I am working as a full stack developer at Padoa.

Experience

Full Stack Engineer @Padoa

Feb 2019 - Present // Paris, France

- Designing and building the application components in Agile environment using Scrum
- Defining the technical solutions for features
- Coding and maintaining the features using Angular for front-end and NodeJS for back-end
- Testing using Jest, Chai and Cypress
- Documenting with flowcharts, layouts and diagrams

Intern as Full Stack Developer @Adias

Feb 2018 - July 2018 // Casablanca, Morocco

- Designed and developed a Web application used for financial audit missions
- Wrote the user stories and define the technical solutions
- Coded using Angular and Spring

Intern as Full Stack Developer @Seo Com

June 2017 - July 2017 // Marrakech, Morocco

- Built a shopping cart site for cosmetic products
- Wrote the user stories and define the technical solutions
- Developed code with PHP using Laravel framework

Education

Software Engineering @Hassania School of Public Works

2015 - 2018 // Casablanca

CPGE - Math & Physics @CPGE Ibn Taymia

2013 - 2015 // Marrakech

Skills

- Team Player
- Problem Solving
- Attention to Details
- Designing & Programming
- Clean Coding
- Software Testing

Tech Stack

Programming Languages

Javascript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, SQL

Libraries & Frameworks

Angular, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Ionic, Elasticsearch, Jest, Cypress

Tools & Platforms

Git, Docker, Firebase, Figma, Photoshop

Projects

Lists ☐

Mobile app built with Ionic for creating and organizing item lists

Awards

2nd Price in ACM – Moroccan Collegiate Programming Contest 2017

Interests

Reading, Traveling, Running, Movies